divine.ca 2013-06-18

# Privacy Policy, divine.ca - divine.ca

**  
divine.ca PRIVACY POLICY**  
At divine.ca, we’re serious about protecting your privacy. The following policy details how we will use your personal information.

INFORMATION COLLECTED AND HOW WE USE IT: You always remain in control of the information you provide to divine.ca. We collect two types of information about visitors: Personal information (such as name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, etc.), which you have voluntarily submitted to us, and Aggregate information (such as information about how many visitors log on to our sites, the pages they access, etc.).

In general, you can visit our website without telling us who you are or revealing personal information about yourself, although you may then not be able to participate in certain promotions. We collect, maintain and use personal information you have voluntarily submitted to contact you, including via email, to respond to your comments or requests for information. We will also use it to communicate with you about the divine.ca service in general, and send any weekly or daily newsletters you’ve subscribed to, as well as sponsored emails on behalf of carefully selected partners in regards to offers, promotions, and new products that may be of interest to you, unless you choose to opt out of these mailings. You can do this by changing your preferences on your profile page and/or clicking the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of any divine.ca email. In addition, we may use personal information to provide you the most helpful and targeted products and services to meet your needs and respond to your inquiries. To better meet your needs, we may supplement the information we collect with data obtained from third parties for the same purposes.

Any contact with our customer service team may be recorded to help us provide better service.

Information posted by individuals on the public idivine profiles, public idivine blogs, public idivine groups, public idivine photo albums, or on divine.ca forums is public and visible to anyone visiting those pages.

DATA SHARING AND TRANSFER: divine.ca will not trade, sell or share your personal information for use by any business, other than the ones to which you submitted your information, without your consent, unless required by law or as disclosed to you when the information is collected. If you do provide us with consent to share your information with other companies, we may share your information with companies who offer products and services that may be of interest to you. These companies may then contact you directly with product or sample offers, personalized offers and information, or to ask for your feedback on products and programs that they think may be of interest to you.

Your personal information will generally be stored in the divine.ca databases, which are located in Canada. Specific information is provided on the web site's consent or registration form, where needed.

You may use divine.ca to invite others to view articles, participate in contests, view your profile, etc. We will use the email addresses you provide only to send an invitation to view the item in question. divine.ca will not sell or share the recipients’ email addresses, or add them to any mailing lists.

You control who sees your idivine profile (automatically created when registering to divine.ca). Be aware that if you choose to make your profile, or any aspects thereof, public on the idivine site, they can be viewed by anyone using the site. 

COOKIES: Cookies help us in many ways to make your visit to our website more enjoyable and meaningful to you. Cookies are text information files that your web browser places on your computer when you visit a website. divine.ca may use such "cookie" technology to obtain non-personal information from you as an online visitor. Most browsers accept cookies automatically, but can be configured not to accept them or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. divine.ca may also use so-called "web beacons" to access the information contained in its cookies within the network of the divine.ca websites and interactive banner ads. 

YOU CAN CHOOSE TO BE CONTACTED OR NOT: Our site allows you to choose, for example, to receive or stop receiving communications from us. If you would like to be removed from divine.ca programs you enrolled in or prevent further use of your personal information, please [click here](http://www.divine.ca/en/divineca/unsubscribe/c_96).

•To Prevent Further Use of Your Personal Information - You will be provided with a way to remove yourself from 

divine.ca’s online programs.  
CHILDREN'S PRIVACY: We take care to protect children's privacy, and abide by national and international laws and regulations on children's privacy. 

SECURITY: We take steps to make all information received from you online as secure as reasonably possible against unauthorized access and use.

ACCESS TO YOUR INFORMATION AND COMPLAINTS: We attempt to keep your files complete, up-to-date, and accurate. You can conveniently access and modify your personal information though your account manager. For email or username changes please contact us: <http://www.divine.ca/en/divineca/contact-us/c_271/>.

We are committed to working with you to obtain a fair and rapid resolution of any complaints or disputes about privacy. Questions regarding our Privacy Statement should be directed to divine.ca inquiries.

LINKS TO OTHER SITES: divine.ca may contain links to other websites. divine.ca has no control over the privacy practices or the content of such websites. We recommend you carefully read the privacy policies of each site you visit. 

YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF OUR PRIVACY PRACTICE: By using this website or any other divine.ca interactive banner ads, you signify your acceptance of our Privacy Statement, and you adhere to the terms and conditions posted on the website.

CHANGES TO THIS POLICY: divine.ca may update or modify this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address you provided us during registration or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

HOW TO CONTACT US: divine.ca is committed to working with consumers to obtain a fair and rapid resolution of any complaints or disputes about privacy. Please send us your questions or comments regarding our privacy practices by clicking on this link   
(<http://www.divine.ca/en/divineca/contact-us/c_271/>) or send a letter to: 

**divine.ca**   
4810 rue Jean-Talon O. suite 203  
Montréal, (QC) H4P 2N5  

Date of Last Revision: January 14, 2010
